{
    "subject": "resource/Victor_Hugo",
    "predicate": "ontology/genre",
    "object": "resource/Dramaturgy",
    "human_readable": "Victor Hugo's genre is Dramaturgy.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9611659049987793,
            "question": "What makes Victor Hugo's work in the genre of Dramaturgy distinctive?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.949654757976532,
            "question": "Give an example of a work by Victor Hugo in the Dramaturgy genre."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8854854106903076,
            "question": "How has Victor Hugo's influence on the Dramaturgy genre been recognized over time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8407626152038574,
            "question": "What was the historical context surrounding Victor Hugo's work in Dramaturgy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6592422127723694,
            "question": "How did Victor Hugo's Dramaturgy contribute to his overall literary legacy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6368957757949829,
            "question": "What literary genre is Victor Hugo known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5520390868186951,
            "question": "Besides writing plays, what other genres did Victor Hugo explore?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5390154123306274,
            "question": "Were there any specific themes or ideas that Victor Hugo explored frequently in his plays?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43874719738960266,
            "question": "Which type of works did Victor Hugo primarily create?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39106518030166626,
            "question": "How did Victor Hugo's understanding of human nature influence his dramatic writing?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Victor Hugo's genre is Dramaturgy.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8037_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which type of works did Victor Hugo primarily create?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8037_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any specific themes or ideas that Victor Hugo explored frequently in his plays?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8037_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Besides writing plays, what other genres did Victor Hugo explore?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8037_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8037_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8037_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8037_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8037_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8037_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8037_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8037_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8037_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8037_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8037_6.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context mentions that \"Opera is above all dramaturgy, and Hugo is probably one of the greatest dramaturgs,\" which supports the statement that Victor Hugo's genre is dramaturgy."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}